<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Pitch Investors Group</string>

    <string name="action_members">Members</string>
    <string name="action_portfolio">Portfolio</string>
    <string name="action_dividends">Dividends</string>
    <string name="action_rules">Rules and Regulations</string>

    <string name="about_group_text"><b><h4>History And Mission</h4></b>
        \n\nRe-Launched in 2015 Pitch Investment Group recovered from non-performance in 2014 due to the fact that investors concentrated heavily on rules and
        regulations instead of the group and investments. Due to this set-back the group relied heavily on investing while implementing the rules. As members we
        do not believe in failure but on ways to improve the company and maintain a very solid foundation.

        \n\nPitch Investors Group, our focus is directed toward evaluating and completing investments in North America and Africa mainly in Energy,
        Resources, Technology, Real Estate and Emerging Markets with appropriate diversification and balance between each division.
        \n\nPitch Investors Group is born from a belief that values-based, sustainable investment practices can enhance return rates.

        \n\nWe target under-valued investments with realistic and immediate appreciation potential and a defined exit strategy.
        Our Investments are not only limited to the latter but Investors can also pitch in any ideas they might have, and the committee will
        evaluate based on a risk assessment.

        \n\n
        <b><h4>Vision Statement</h4></b>
        \n\nTo emerge from the position of domestic leader to leading global player in the investment sector by adopting best practices
        and wise analytics before investments and decision making.

        \n\n
        <b><h4>Mission Statement</h4></b>
        \n\nWe are committed to enriching society by delivering superior investment services. We are not afraid to continually challenge conventional wisdom and actively
        encourage change in order to pursue growth. We are committed to putting our clients at the heart of our business, developing and maintaining long-standing relationships
        based on trust. We are one firm, committed to delivering the full range of our capabilities, knowledge and resources to meet the needs of our clients. We respect diversity
        and value differences of opinion.
    </string>

    <string name="members_group_text">
    <b>Peter Mbanda</b>
    \n<i>Chairman</i>
    \nWith Pitch Investors Group since inception 2014, maintains and co\'ordinate as well as oversee the groups performance. Also responsible
    for organising the group meetings and active participant in groups decision making and strategy.

    \n\n<b>Anthony Karanja</b>
    \n<i>Committee</i>
    \nAnthony joined Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible for the groups core decision making process. Anthony brings his skills as an analyst and
    strategist.  As a member of the investment committee he has a key role in shaping our approach to sustainable, responsible investing (SRI) portfolios.

    \n\n<b>Victor Muiruri</b>
    \n<i>Committee</i>
    \nVictor joined Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible for the groups core decision making process. Victor brings his skills as a day-to-day
    trader.  As a member of the investment committee he has a key role in shaping our approach to sustainable, responsible investing (SRI) portfolios.

    \n\n<b>David Kyrupt</b>
    \n<i>Committee</i>
    \nDavid joined Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible for the groups core decision making process. David brings his skills as an analyst and
    strategist.  As a member of the investment committee he has a key role in shaping our approach to sustainable, responsible investing (SRI) portfolios.


    \n\n<b>Levi Mwirigi</b>
    \n<i>Member</i>
    \nLevi started at Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible as a member to ensure performance by the board members. Holds one vote as
    a stake holder and responsible for electing members into the board.

    \n\n<b>Njenga Kihumba</b>
    \n<i>Member</i>
    \nNjenga started at Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible as a member to ensure performance by the board members. Holds one vote as
    a stake holder and responsible for electing members into the board.

    \n\n<b>Bernard Kairu</b>
    \n<i>Member</i>
    \nBernard started at Pitch Investors Group in the latter half of 2015. He is responsible as a member to ensure performance by the board members. Holds one vote as
    a stake holder and responsible for electing members into the board.

    \n\n<b>Brian Kiarie</b>
    \n<i>Member</i>
    \nBrian started at Pitch Investors Group in 2015. He is responsible as a member to ensure performance by the board members. Holds one vote as
    a stake holder and responsible for electing members into the board.
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_members">Members (PIG)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_portfolio">Portfolio (PIG)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dividends">Dividends (PIG)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rules">Rules (PIG)</string>

    <string name="rules_group_text"> When you start an investment club, you are starting a business and you need to decide on what type of business operating structure you will use.
        Different business types have different operating, federal and state reporting and taxation requirements.

        \n\nWe recommend you operate as a general partnership. This is the simplest structure to use when a group of people conduct business together.
        Setting up a general partnership is simple. You register a name, get an EIN number and develop and sign a partnership agreement.
        Each year you will need to file a federal and possibly a state partnership tax return. They are informational returns.
        A partnership is a \"pass through\" entity. All of it\'s income is distributed yearly to the partners.
        Taxes are paid by each partner on their portion on their individual tax returns. Pitch Investors Group is designed to let you easily do the accounting for a general partnership.
        It uses your accounting data to quickly generate the federal tax return Form 1065 your investment club needs to file each year.


        \n\nSometimes people are concerned because members of a general partnership have personal liability for the actions of the partnership.
        This applies only when partners are acting within the defined boundaries of the partnerships business. The purpose of your partnership should be clearly
        spelled out in your partnership agreement. The only purpose of the partnership is to invest the assets of the partnership solely in stocks, bonds,
        and other securities for the education and benefit of the
        partners.\"


        \n\nWithin these constraints, if you file the necessary tax returns each year, it is unlikely that your partnership would incur any liability that you would
        cause you any personal issues. Many clubs have operated for many years successfully as general partnerships without any problems that we are aware of.
        For simplicity, we suggest you use this business set up.


        \n\nDespite this, some clubs want to consider operating as an LLC or Limited Liability Company. Within an LLC, each members personal liability is generally
        limited to their percent of ownership. Limited Liability Companies are set up with your state and do require additional annual reporting and fees. In general, however,
        they do have the same tax reporting requirements as general partnerships. This means that Pitch Investors Group would still provide your club with the accounting
        and tax forms that you would need to file.



        \n\nWe do get questions every now and then about whether a group should set themselves up as a corporation. We would highly discourage this. With a corporation,
        you will have much more complicated operating and state reporting requirements. Pitch Investors Group does not provide the accounting or produce the taxes you would need to
        file as a corporation. If you feel you must run your investment group as a corporation, you should do so with outside professional legal and
        accounting guidance.</string>


    <string name="portfolio_group_text">
        <b>Type of Investment</b>
        \n<i>Stock</i>
        \n\n<b>Chesapeake Energy</b> <i>Symbol \(chk\)</i>
        \nDescription
        \n\nChesapeake Energy Corporation engages in the acquisition, exploration, and development of properties for the production of oil,
        natural gas, and natural gas liquids from underground reservoirs in the United States. The company holds interests in natural gas resource plays,
        Louisiana and East Texas. The Marcellus Shale in Pennsylvania and the Barnett Shale in South Texas.
        The Utica Shale in Ohio and Pennsylvania, the Anadarko Basin in Oklahoma and the Texas Panhandle; and the Niobrara Shale in Wyoming.
        The company owns interests in approximately 32,400 oil and natural gas wells. Chesapeake Energy Corporation was founded
        in 1989 and is headquartered in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma.

        \n\n<i>Stock</i>
        \n\n<b>Sprint Corporation</b> <i>Symbol \(s\)</i>
        \nDescription
        \n\nSprint Corporation, through its subsidiaries, provides various wireless and wire line communications products and services to consumers,
        businesses, government subscribers, and resellers in the United States, Puerto Rico, and the U.S. Virgin Islands.
        The Wireless segment offers wireless data communication services, including mobile productivity applications, such as Internet access,
        messaging, and email services. The Wire line segment provides wire line voice and data communications, including domestic and
        international data communications using various protocols, such as multi protocol label switching technologies,
        Internet protocol (IP), managed network services, Voice over IP, session initiated protocol, and traditional voice services
        to other communications companies. Sprint Corporation is a subsidiary of SoftBank Group Corp.

    </string>
</resources>

